Robert Schoelkopf Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artist Files, 1851-1991, undated, Series 1:; (boxes 1-23, 23 linear ft.)
  - Evans, Walker (Box 6)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1966-1977, undated (Box 6)
    - Photographs of the Artist, [circa 1966, circa 1974] (Box 6)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 6)
  - Fenton, Roger, General, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Field, Hamilton Easter, General, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Fiore, Joseph A., General, 1965-1970, undated (Box 6)
  - Fiske, Gertrude (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1989, undated, (3 folders) (Box 6)
    - Exhibition Lists and Inventories, 1969-1975, undated (Box 6)
    - Printed Material, Announcements, Catalogs, 1969-1975, 1991, undated (Box 6)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1966-1975, undated (Box 6)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated, (3 folders) (Box 6)
  - Flannagan, John Bernard, General, 1984-1988, undated (Box 7)
  - Fockersperger, Wilhelm, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Frazier, John Robinson, General, 1969-1970, undated (Box 7)
  - Freckelton, Sondra (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1991, (4 folders) (Box 7)
    - Inventory Sheets, 1987-1988, undated (Box 7)
    - Printed Material, 1983-1991, undated (Box 7)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated, (3 folders) (Box 7)
  - Freund, Gisèle (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1977, (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - Printed Material, 1975-1982, undated (Box 7)
    - Printed Material-Clippings, 1975-1976, undated (Box 7)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 7)
  - Friedman, Arnold, General, undated (Box 7)
  - Frieseke, Frederick C., Photographs of Works of Art, 1955, undated (Box 7)
  - Garman, Ed (Box 7)
    - General, 1990-1991 (Box 7)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 7)
  - Gay, Walter, General, undated (Box 7)
  - Gee, Yun (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1969, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Printed Material, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1968, 1981-1988, undated (Box 7)
  - Genthe, Arnold, General, 1975, undated (Box 7)
  - Gifford, Sanford Robinson, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 7)
  - Gillespie, Frances Cohen (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1979, undated (Box 7)
    - Printed Material, 1976-1978 (Box 7)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 7)
  - Glackens, William J., Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 7)
  - Gleizes, Albers, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 7)
  - Goodnough, Robert, General, 1962-1964, undated (Box 7)
  - Goodwin, Arthur Clifton, General, 1973, undated (Box 7)
  - Gorky, Arshile (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1985 (Box 7)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 7)
  - Grafly, Charles, Correspondence, 1963, undated (Box 7)
  - Graham, John, General, 1960, 1973, undated (Box 7)
  - Grausman, Philip (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1991, undated, (4 folders) (Box 7)
    - Printed Material, Announcements, Catalogs, 1974-1989, undated (Box 7)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1961-1989, undated (Box 7)
    - Photographs of the Artist, 1990, undated (Box 7)
  - Graves, Morris, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 7)
  - Gris, Juan, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 7)
  - Groshans, Werner, General, 1969-1972, undated (Box 7)
  - Guglielmi, Louis (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1991, undated, (gallery's representation of Guglielmi's estate) (Box 7)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 7)
  - Guy, James M. (Box 8)
    - General, 1990-1991, undated (Box 8)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 8)
  - Han, Raymond (Box 8)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1991, undated, (5 folders) (Box 8)
    - Printed Material, 1982-1991 (Box 8)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated, (3 folders) (Box 8)
  - Harding, Goodwin, General, 1975-1977 (Box 8)
  - Hardy, DeWitt (Box 8)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1991, (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Printed Material, 1979-1986, undated (Box 8)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 8)
  - Hartley, Marsden (Box 8)
    - General, 1961-1986, undated (Box 8)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, n.d, (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Hartman, Bertram C. (Box 8)
    - Photographs of the Artist, 1946, undated (Box 8)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 8)
  - Harvey, Anne, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 8)
  - Hassam, Childe, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 8)
  - Hatke, Walter (Box 8)
    - Consignment Records, 1982-1989 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1991, undated, (4 folders) (Box 8)
    - Printed Material, 1975-1986, undated (Box 8)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1978-1982, undated, (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Hawthorne, Charles Webster, General, 1963-1965, undated (Box 8)
  - Heade, Martin Johnson, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 8)
  - Henri, Robert, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 8)
  - Hine, Lewis Wickes, General, 1974-1978, undated (Box 8)
  - Hopkinson, Charles, General, 1955-1969, undated (Box 8)
  - Horton, William S. (Box 8)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1968 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1979, undated (Box 8)
    - Exhibition Lists and Inventories, circa 1968-1969 (Box 8)
    - Printed Material, Announcements, Catalogs, 1967-circa 1968 (Box 8)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1968-1969, undated (Box 8)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 8)
  - Huffman, Laton Alton, General, 1974-1979, undated (Box 8)
  - Hunt, William Morris, Photograph of Work of Art, undated (Box 8)
  - Hutson, Charles Woodward (Box 8)
    - Printed Material, 1921-1931, undated (Box 8)
    - Photographs of the Artist, circa 1928-1934, undated (Box 8)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 8)
  - Ito, Miyako (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1971, 1991, undated, (4 folders; illustrated letters; 1961 contains letter folded as origami) (Box 9)
    - Printed Material, 1960-1971, undated (Box 9)
  - Jacobshagen, Keith (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1987, undated, (2 folders; 5 illustrated letters) (Box 9)
    - Printed Material, 1979-1987, undated (Box 9)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1969, 1980-1985, undated, (4 folders) (Box 9)
  - John, Augustus, General, undated (Box 9)
  - Johnson, Ben, General, 1957-1973, undated (Box 9)
  - Johnson, David, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 9)
  - Johnson, Eastman, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 9)
  - Johnson, Lester, General, 1983, undated (Box 9)
  - Jonson, Raymond, General, 1972-1983, undated (Box 9)
  - Kane, John, General, 1966, undated (Box 9)
  - Karfiol, Bernard, Correspondence, 1964 (Box 9)
  - Karfunkle, David, General, 1911, 1962-1963, undated (Box 9)
  - Keiley, Joseph, Correspondence, 1977, undated (Box 9)
  - Kelpe, Paul, General, 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - Kensett, John Frederick, General, undated (Box 9)
  - Kertész, André, General, 1965-1974, undated, (photograph by Kertész of [Robert Schoelkopf] labeled "Spring, 1971, after fire") (Box 9)
  - King, William, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 9)
  - Kirchner, Ernst Ludwig, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 9)
  - Klee, Paul, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 9)
  - Klimt, Gustav, General, undated (Box 9)
  - Kline, Franz, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 9)
  - Knaths, Karl, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 9)
  - Kopman, Benjamin, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 9)
  - Kruger, Louise, General, 1955-1973, undated (Box 9)
  - Kuhn, Walt, General, 1965, 1975, 1983, undated (Box 9)
  - Kumler, Kipton (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1979, undated (Box 9)
    - Printed Material, 1975-1977, undated (Box 9)
  - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 9)
  - Lachaise, Gaston (Box 9)
    - Accounting Records, 1963-1989, (3 folders) (Box 9)
    - Appraisals, 1962-1989, undated (Box 9)
    - Australian Galleries, 1977-1980 (Box 9)
    - Authentication Letters, 1963-1990, undated (Box 9)
    - Casting Records, 1971-1990, undated (Box 9)
    - Consignment Records, 1977-1989, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1964, undated, (3 folders) (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1991, (13 folders) (Box 10)
    - Dial Collection, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
    - Drawing Records, 1962-1991, undated (Box 10)
    - Exhibition, undated (Box 10)
    - Exhibition (1973), Robert Schoelkopf Gallery, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 10)
    - Exhibition (1974), University of California, Los Angeles, and Cornell University, 1972-1975 (Box 10)
    - Exhibition (1978), Robert Schoelkopf Gallery, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Exhibition (1979), University of Rochester Memorial Art Gallery, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
    - Exhibition 1982), Robert Schoelkopf Gallery, 1981-1982, undated (Box 10)
    - Exhibition (1983), Portland Museum of Art, 1983-1984, undated (Box 10)
    - Exhibition (1985), PS Galleries, 1983-1985 (Box 10)
    - Exhibition (1985-1986), National Portrait Gallery, 1983-1986, undated (Box 10)
    - Exhibition (1985-1986), National Portrait Gallery, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 10)
    - Exhibition, Traveling Show, 1966-1971, undated, (7 folders) (Box 10)
    - Exhibition, Traveling Show, 1972-1990, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Lachaise Foundation Purchases, 1966-1989 (Box 11)
    - Modern Art Foundry, Inc., 1962-1990 (Box 11)
    - Printed Material, Announcements, Catalogs, 1956-1982, undated, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1925-1985, undated, (4 folders) (Box 11)
    - Publication, Eakins Press, 1966-1973, undated (Box 11)
    - Publication, Harry N. Abrams, Inc., 1969-1980, undated (Box 11)
    - R. W. Norton Gallery, 1963-1981, undated (Box 11)
    - Sculpture Labels, undated (Box 11)
    - Sculpture Location Records, 1984-1991 (Box 11)
    - Tallix Foundry, 1983-1988 (Box 11)
    - Works Offered to Clients, 1969-1990, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Photographs of Installations, 1963-1969, undated, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, Bronzes, 1985, undated, (5 folders) (Box 11)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, Drawings, undated, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, Plasters, undated, (4 folders) (Box 11)
    - Photographs of Works of Art in Storage, undated (Box 11)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 11)
  - Laderman, Gabriel (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1991, undated, (6 folders) (Box 12)
    - Printed Material, Announcements, Catalogs, 1964-1990, undated (Box 12)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1964-1991, undated (Box 12)
    - Photographs of Installations, 1969 (Box 12)
    - Photograph [of the artist], undated (Box 12)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1966-1985, undated, (6 folders) (Box 12)
  - Lawrence, Jacob, General, 1969, undated (Box 12)
  - Lawson, Ernest, General, 1967, undated (Box 12)
  - Lechay, Myron (Box 12)
    - General, 1964-1987, (several essays written by Lechay; copy of a letter from Lechay's brother concerning the artist's personality and work) (Box 12)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 12)
  - Leibowitz, Leonard, General, 1965-1971 (Box 12)
  - Levinson, Abraham F., General, 1931-1947, undated, (2 pencil drawings by Levinson, one entitled George Luks) (Box 12)
  - Ligare, David (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1991, undated, (3 folders) (Box 12)
    - Printed Material, Announcements, Catalogs, 1978-1988, undated (Box 12)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1984-1990, undated (Box 12)
    - Photographs of Installations, 1986 (Box 12)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1981-1989, undated, (3 folders) (Box 12)
  - Luks, George, General, 1973-1987, undated (Box 13)
  - Lummis, Charles F., General, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
  - MacDonald-Wright, Stanton, General, 1979-1986, undated (Box 13)
  - MacPherson, Robert, General, 1975-1977 (Box 13)
  - Mager, Gus, General, 1963, undated (Box 13)
  - Manolo, General, 1964-1965, undated (Box 13)
  - Manship, Paul (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1988, undated, (legal agreements relating to Schoelkopf's role as agent of the Manship estate) (Box 13)
    - Printed Material, 1966-1986, undated (Box 13)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 13)
  - Marin, John, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 13)
  - Marini, Marino (Box 13)
    - Photograph of the Artist, undated (Box 13)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 13)
  - Marks, Charles, General, 1966-1970, undated (Box 13)
  - Martini, Arturo, General, 1967, undated (Box 13)
  - Matthiasdottir, Louisa (Box 13)
    - Accounting and Consignment Records, 1966-1990 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1991, undated, (7 folders) (Box 13)
    - Printed Material, Announcements, Catalogs, 1964-1991, undated (Box 13)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1961-1989, undated (Box 13)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1974-1985, undated, (6 folders) (Box 13)
  - Matulka, Jan (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1928-1933, 1969-1990, undated, (3 folders) (Box 14)
    - Exhibition (1988), Robert Schoelkopf Gallery, 1988 (Box 14)
    - Exhibition, Traveling Show, 1978-1981, undated, (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Lida J. Matulka Estate, 1970-1989, undated, (2 folders; legal documentation and notes regarding appraisal and subsequent handling of works of art in Lida J. Matulka's estate) (Box 14)
    - Printed Material, Announcements, Catalogs, 1925-1990, undated (Box 14)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1925-1990, undated (Box 14)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated, (8 folders) (Box 14)
  - Maurer, Alfred Henry, General, 1967-1987, undated (Box 14)
  - McFee, Henry (Box 14)
    - General, 1944, 1969-1986 (Box 14)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1970, undated (Box 14)
  - McIlvain, Isabel (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1991, (3 folders) (Box 14)
    - Printed Material, 1976-1990 (Box 14)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 14)
  - Mestler, Ludwig, Biographical Material, 1961 (Box 14)
  - Metcalf, Willard Leroy, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 14)
  - Mondrian, Piet, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 14)
  - Moore, Henry, Photographs of Works of Art, undated, (3 folders) (Box 14)
  - Moran, Thomas, General, undated (Box 15)
  - Moskowitz, Ira, General, 1963-1964, undated (Box 15)
  - Müller, Jan, General, 1962-1967 (Box 15)
  - Muller, Lisa, General, 1965, undated (Box 15)
  - Muray, Nikolas, General, 1969-1974, undated (Box 15)
  - Murch, Walter, Photograph of Work of Art, undated (Box 15)
  - Muybridge, Eadweard, General, 1973-1983, undated (Box 15)
  - Myers, Ethel (Box 15)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1976, undated, (3 folders) (Box 15)
    - Printed Material, 1966 (Box 15)
    - Photographs of Installations, [1963] (Box 15)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 15)
  - Myers, Jerome, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 15)
  - Myers, Joan, General, 1976-1981 (Box 15)
  - Nadelman, Elie (Box 15)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Printed Material, 1966-1985, undated (Box 15)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1977, 1980, undated, (7 folders; related printed material) (Box 15)
  - Nevelson, Louise, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 15)
  - Nick, George Bentley (Box 15)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 15)
    - Printed Material, 1965-1969, undated (Box 15)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1970, undated (Box 15)
  - Of, George F., Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 15)
  - O'Keeffe, Georgia (Box 15)
    - General, 1970-1985, undated (Box 15)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1966, undated (Box 15)
  - Orozco, José Clemente, General, 1962-1967, undated (Box 15)
  - Patterson, Charles, General, 1950-1991, undated (Box 15)
  - Pearlstein, Philip, General, 1980-1984, undated, (photograph of Portrait of Robert Schoelkopf) (Box 15)
  - Peterson, Jane (Box 15)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1989 (Box 15)
    - Printed Material, 1968-1977, undated (Box 15)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 15)
  - Peto, John Frederick, General, 1975-1978, undated (Box 15)
  - Picasso, Pablo, General, 1969, undated (Box 15)
  - Piccolo, Richard (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1991, undated, (3 folders) (Box 16)
    - Printed Material, 1975-1988 (Box 16)
    - Photographs of the Artist, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1980-1985, undated, (3 folders, 0.5 slide box stored in Box 21) (Box 16)
  - Pippin, Horace, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 16)
  - Pollet, Joseph, General, 1964-1968, undated (Box 16)
  - Pollock, Jackson, General, 1976, undated (Box 16)
  - Powers, Hiram, General, 1968-1986, undated (Box 16)
  - Prendergast, Maurice Brazil, General, 1985, undated (Box 16)
  - Quin, Langdon (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, circa 1980-1991, (handmade card) (Box 16)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1988-1990, undated (Box 16)
  - Rabinovitch, Ben Magid, Printed Material, 1945-1949, undated (Box 16)
  - Raiselis, Richard, Correspondence, 1983-1991 (Box 16)
  - Raymond, Lilo, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 16)
  - Reich, Murray, General, 1963-1964 (Box 16)
  - Reid, Robert, General, 1981, n.d (Box 16)
  - Richards, William Trost, General, undated (Box 16)
  - Richardt, Ferdinand, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 16)
  - Riis, Jacob A., Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 16)
  - Rimmer, William, General, 1966-1979, undated (Box 16)
  - Rivera, Diego, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 16)
  - Roberts, Stone (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1991, undated, (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Printed Material, 1986-1989, undated (Box 16)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1981-1988, undated, (1 folder, 0.33 slide box stored in Box 21) (Box 16)
  - Rodin, Auguste (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1981 (Box 16)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1983, undated (Box 16)
  - Rogers, Randolph, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Rosenblatt, Adolph (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1972, undated (Box 16)
    - Printed Material, 1966-1968 (Box 16)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1966, undated (Box 16)
  - Russell, Morgan, General, 1980-1985 (Box 16)
  - Ryan, Richard (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1989, undated (Box 16)
    - Printed Material, 1984-1990 (Box 16)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1981-1988, undated, (1 folder, 0.33 slide box stored in Box 21) (Box 16)
  - Ryder, Albert Pinkham, General, undated (Box 16)
  - Saari, Peter (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1991, undated, (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Printed Material, 1982-1990 (Box 16)
    - Photographs of Installations and Works of Art, 1987-1990, undated, (color transparencies of the artist at work, some apparently at the Kovner-Peter residence in Millbrook, New York) (Box 16)
  - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus, General, 1987, undated (Box 16)
  - Salemme, Antonio (Box 17)
    - General, 1964-1969 (Box 17)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 17)
  - Salemme, Attilio, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 17)
  - Sander, August (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1981 (Box 17)
    - Printed Material, 1975-1979, undated (Box 17)
  - Sargent, John Singer, General, 1964-1969, undated (Box 17)
  - Scarlett, Rolph (Box 17)
    - General, 1982-1991, undated (Box 17)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 17)
  - Schamberg, Morton L. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 17)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 17)
  - Schiele, Egon, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 17)
  - Schmidt, Edward (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1991, undated, (2 folders; illustrated postcard in 1984) (Box 17)
    - Printed Material, 1980-1990, undated (Box 17)
    - Photographs of Installations and Works of Art, 1975-1986, undated, (1 folder, 0.33 slide box stored in Box 21) (Box 17)
  - Schmidt, Elsa, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 17)
  - Schussele, Christian, General, 1971-1976, undated (Box 17)
  - Sears, Sarah Choate, General, 1963, undated (Box 17)
  - Severio, Gino, General, undated (Box 17)
  - Shahn, Ben, General, 1970, undated, (2 letters from Walker Evans certifying authenticity of 2 paintings by Shahn given to him in exchange for work of his own) (Box 17)
  - Shaw, Charles Green, General, undated (Box 17)
  - Shaw, Sydney Dale, General, 1966-1981 (Box 17)
  - Shechter, Laura (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 17)
    - Printed Material, 1980-1987, undated (Box 17)
  - Sheeler, Charles, General, 1963-1986, undated (Box 17)
  - Shinn, Everett, General, [1961], undated (Box 17)
  - Shinn, Florence Scovel, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 17)
  - Sklarski, Bonnie (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1991, undated (Box 17)
    - Printed Material, 1976-1991 (Box 17)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1975, undated, (1 folder, 0.33 slide box stored in Box 21) (Box 17)
  - Sommer, Frederick, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 17)
  - Sommer, Giorgio, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 17)
  - Spencer, Niles, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 17)
  - Staples, W. L., General, 1965-1966, undated (Box 17)
  - Stearns, Junius Brutus, General, 1972, undated (Box 17)
  - Steichen, Edward, General, 1969-1981, undated (Box 17)
  - Stella, Joseph (Box 17)
    - Biographical and Source Material, 1929, undated, (part of a memoir, handwritten, probably by Stella) (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, circa 1944, 1960-1991, undated, (6 folders; letter from August Mosca describing personal memories of Stella and Stella's silverpoint technique in 1983) (Box 17)
    - Estate Records, 1963-1991 (Box 17)
    - Exhibition Lists, 1963-1979, undated (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 18)
    - Printed Material, Announcements, Catalogs, 1930-1990, undated (Box 18)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1924-1991, undated (Box 18)
    - Publication, Irma Jaffe, 1963-1970 (Box 18)
    - Rabin & Kruger Gallery, 1960-1986, undated (Box 18)
    - Photograph of the Artist, undated (Box 18)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, 1963-1984, undated, (6 folders, 0.33 slide box stored in Box 21) (Box 18)
  - Sterne, Maurice, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 18)
  - Stieglitz, Alfred, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 18)
  - Stone, Louis, General, 1940-1969, 1985-1991, undated (Box 18)
  - Stone, Sandra, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 18)
  - Storrs, John Henry Bradley (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1991, undated, (9 folders) (Box 18)
    - Estate Transfer and Contracts, 1969-1986, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Exhibition (1986-1987), Whitney Museum of American Art, 1965-1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Gifts, 1974-1977 (Box 18)
    - Loan to Clark Art Institute, 1979-1980, undated (Box 18)
    - Printed Material, Announcements, Catalogs, 1920-1988 (Box 18)
    - Printed Material, Clippings, 1925-1989, undated (Box 18)
    - Platinum Prints, undated, (11 prints attributed to Storrs) (Box 19)
    - Silver Gelatin Prints, undated, (27 prints attributed to Storrs) (Box 19)
    - Photographs of Installations, 1975-1981, undated (Box 19)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, Downtown Gallery, undated, (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, Noel Frackman Publicity Material, circa 1986, (1 folder, 0.33 slide box stored in Box 21) (Box 19)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, Warehouse, 1977, undated (Box 19)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, Winnetka, undated (Box 19)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, Miscellaneous Media, undated (Box 19)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, Paintings, undated, (4 folders) (Box 19)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, Sculpture, 1981, 1987, undated, (4 folders) (Box 19)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, Works on Paper, undated, (3 folders) (Box 19)
  - Strand, Paul, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Suba, Miklos (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1991, undated, (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Printed Material, 1964-1983, undated (Box 19)
    - Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 19)
  - Tack, Augustus Vincent, General, 1945, 1983-1988 (Box 19)
  - Tamayo, Rufino, Photographs of Works of Art, undated (Box 19)